This is just gonna be two weeks
of moping and tedious emo songs...
(Sheldon:)...and calling me to come down
to pet stores to look at cats.
(Sheldon:)I don't know if I can take it.
(Raj:)You could power down.
(Howard:)Well, as usual,
Wolowitz has the solution.
(Howard:)I happen to know a place
where there are plenty of eligible women...
(Howard:)...and Leonard could have his pick.
[LATIN MUSIC PLAYS OVER SPEAKERS]
(Class instructor:)Remember the Latin hips.
(Class instructor:)Shoulders stay still and we sway.
(Class instructor:)One, two, three.
(Class instructor:)Five, six, seven.
(Howard(to Leonard):)I think Mrs. Tishman's
got her eye on you.
(Howard(to Leonard):)I've been there. You're in for a treat.